Not even a goodbye?
Come on in.
Blacklisted before I even graduate.
That's got to be your record.
I don't know who you ticked off around here,
but you sure ruffled some feathers.
I have enemies in high places.
Well, we're going to miss you.
You're right.
You're just going to miss the free proofreader.
Max, your wife's called three times about dinner.
Tell her I'm on my way.
Seriously, if there's anything I can ever do...
Actually, um, it's just a few stories I've been working on.
I would love for you to take a look at them.
Chloe, I couldn't print your name.
I'm in the classifieds right now without catching Al.
Well, what about a pseudonym?
She's my cousin.
She won't mind at all.
She's not interested in journalism.
Lois Lane.
I was looking for the on-call tech guy.
Well, you found her.
You work in the tech department?
Would you rather have a PlayStation-addicted dork
wearing a Star Wars T-shirt?
Molly.
Lex.
So what's the crisis, Lex?
Well, I'm trying to finish a presentation.
My program keeps crashing,
and I don't have the time to deal with it.
Probably a virus.
I would assume so.
You know, I've only been back a few weeks,
but I'm surprised I haven't seen you.
Back from where?
It's a long story.
I.e., none of my business.
There we go.
This should scan for any viruses.
You would do it yourself, or you need me to do it for you?
I think I can handle it.
I can handle it.
Unplugged.
Pete, what happened to my computers?
A bunch of delivery men stopped by this afternoon.
Luthor Corp. took the computers back.
But they were donated.
Yeah, well, I guess a Grinch changed his mind.
Oh, yeah, some girl stopped by.
Didn't leave a name.
Thanks, Pete.
I had nothing to lose.
Now names can be thereafter.
I take herыс.
Th.
End?
I met her sour first time over.
Ancient.
Chloe?
Stay, stay, come on.
I've been waiting for you.
Stay.
I've made this whole world shine for you.
Stay, stay, come on.
The last thing I remember, I was in the library.
I was working on my history paper.
Stone sober.
Miss Sullivan, would you care to shed any light
on Mr. Kent's version of the incident?
What do you mean, the part where I wasn't eating pavement?
I don't know. Um...
It just...
It looked like he lost control of his truck.
Well, Mr. Kent,
your family sure has its way of going through vehicles.
Chloe?
Is that all you need from Clark?
Why don't you go on home?
I got a few more questions for our Miss Sullivan.
I'll be right back.
I'm glad you're feeling better, Adam.
Clark, are you okay?
I just heard about the accident.
I'm okay.
Chloe's a little scraped up.
Um, Clark, this is Adam.
Nice to finally meet you.
So you're Clark.
Heard a lot about you.
Didn't realize there was that much to say.
How'd you get here so quickly?
Oh, no, I was just upstairs visiting Adam.
Physical therapy.
Isn't that where you two met?
Yeah, I thought I'd see you when you dropped by to visit Lana,
but I guess you got busy.
Looks like we've all been busy.
I guess so.
Ever since Lex gave me this thing,
it's like no one can change a coffee filter on their own.
Mr. Luther.
Where's Molly?
Uh, Molly?
Yeah.
She was working here last night.
She loaned me this.
Ah, I've been looking for that.
We don't have a Molly.
I was the one on call last night.
From home.
Well, she was here unpacking these computer boxes.
Huh, well, that might explain how all those hard drives got wiped out.
We can't do that just yet.
Oh.
There is a lot going on in that cup.
Well, it is your first time here.
I'm trying really hard to get the thumbs up.
This place has really been a refuge for me.
Refuge from what?
Well, just everything.
It was interesting meeting Clark.
We're just friends.
Just friends?
Well, for friends, you're very uncomfortable
around each other.
Yeah, well, we've got a lot of history.
I saw the way he looked at you.
Clark doesn't know what he wants.
Besides, I can't control the way he feels.
And you?
Clark will always be a very important part of my life.
But whatever there was between us, it's gone.
If you're looking for signs of tampering,
I'll save you some time.
There's nothing wrong with it.
I asked the mechanic.
There's got to be some explanation.
As to why you tried to mow me over?
I'm ready and waiting.
Didn't you tell the sheriff that I lost control of the truck?
I was covering for you, Clark.
You chased me onto the sidewalk.
Now, I know.
I know.
I know that you're still upset with me
about this whole Lionel thing.
But don't you think that manslaughter is
a little beyond eye for an eye?
Chloe, you don't think I tried to hurt you?
I don't know.
The way you've been acting lately, I don't know, Clark.
I can only apologize so many times.
I have been having a hard time getting over this.
Every time I see you, I can't help picturing
you and Lionel talking.
And you're not the same person you used to be.
Kind of like if I moved
to Metropolis and became a motorcycle-riding party animal
and told you to get out of my life.
Kind of like that, right?
Look, you know what?
As much fun as this guilt trip is,
I came here to see if you put any more pieces
together from last night.
What happened after the library?
I don't even remember leaving the library.
Last thing I do remember, I was working on my laptop.
I was working on my laptop.
I don't know a polygon or anything like that either.
I just don't have as much time to do my homework,
and I got a little thoughtless pee-tee,
so I'm just gonna sit here.
I'll be gonna go away for quite a while
and show you something headed for the lab tonight.
Thanks.
That computer really must be in the gallery.
Oh, the computer recovered your paper.
That's an interesting take on General Sherman.
I didn't even finish my sentence.
Iasha-
It says they downloaded an email before the accident, but it won't open.
Who's Brainwave?
Remind me again what your school mascot is.
Oh, wait, it's a bird.
Okay, it's a small town. We take our school spirit very seriously.
Oh, I forgot my history book. I'll meet you outside.
Okay.
I'll meet you outside.
Lana, hey, I've been looking for you.
Lana, what are you doing?
Killing Chloe Sullivan.
Please don't.
No!
No, Anya!
Help!
ứ
Do Not!
No!
Puddle towel!
What is mission road for me.
Shall we run away with here?
Follow me, please!
Trust me!
I love you.
Where are you?
Here.
I want to show you the secret.
Places to go, where?
As I said to accept your help.
I tried.
I was running over.
Take my finger and give it to me.
Definitely will.
Tell me your secret code?
It's still there.
Not here.
Ci e.
You bastard.
What happened?
So we can rule out paranoia.
Someone is officially trying to kill me.
Not just someone.
Yeah, well, either way, it still doesn't look great for me.
Chloe, I'm so sorry.
I can't believe I went after you like that.
Yeah.
I can't believe you got us suspended.
Thankfully, Adam was there.
Some really nice moves.
What was that? Kung fu? Judo?
I don't know.
I guess I've watched a few too many Jackie Chan movies.
Well, who would have thought it would come in handy
in the treacherous halls of Smallville High?
Just before this, did you get any weird e-mails?
Let me check.
I did, but I don't remember opening it.
I was trying to find it.
It sounds like the same thing happened to both of us.
It's like we were being hypnotized.
It could be a subliminal message.
Something could have been hidden in the binary codes.
How did I get snapped out of it?
Right now, I'm a little bit more concerned
with what triggered the kill Chloe impulse in the first place.
It's brainwave again.
I don't know.
Every computer online has an IP address,
so we should be able to...
to track the message with the computer that it was sent from.
You can do that.
We'll see.
If this brainwave person wanted me dead so badly,
why didn't they just send me a message saying to off myself?
The brain's hardwired to stay alive.
I mean, not even hypnotic messages can override
our survival instincts.
Don't you just pick that up somewhere?
I was in physical rehab for months.
What else is there to do but read?
Chloe, the message came from your computer.
I thought Lionel took back all of your computers.
Why would anyone at Luther Corp want to attack you?
Look, I hate to think you wasted a trip to Metropolis,
but I seriously doubt my father's trying to kill Chloe.
Why?
He was willing to put his own son in a mental institution.
You know what he's capable of.
Clark, what reason would he have to go after a high school
reporter from Smallville?
Is there something you're not telling me?
Does this have anything to do with the seven weeks of my life
I can't remember?
All I know is that Lionel asked you to fire Chloe's dad.
Look, Clark, that was business.
You know, contrary to common perception,
my father isn't behind every nefarious activity
in Smallville.
Besides, he'd never be that circuitous.
Those emails can't be trusted.
They're not.
Those emails came from Chloe's computer
after it was packed up and shipped to Luther Corp.
Who else would have access?
Dr. Garner, how are things at Summerhall?
Is everything OK?
Oh, I wish I could say it was.
Reporter from the Daily Planet stopped by today.
His name was Mac.
Mac?
Mac's Taylor.
About that horrible article that girl wrote?
Unfortunately.
I just don't know what I'm going to do if they shut me down.
Think about all the people that I've helped.
Where will they go?
That's never going to happen.
I don't know.
I just can't seem to get them to leave us alone.
How can I make them understand, Molly?
You can't.
They'll never understand.
I'm just glad I was able to help you so much.
If these reporters have their way, other patients may not be so lucky.
This is a very good thing.
It's a very good thing.
I know that.
Are you leaving?
Ha. Parole. Good behavior.
So are you.
Heading back to Metropolis?
I was sort of thinking about staying in Smallville.
Why?
Ow.
That hurt.
No, I just meant, you know, after what I did at the school,
Smallville just doesn't seem like the type of place you'd go to
if you could go anywhere.
Actually, it's about as close to home as I have.
And I was hoping I could spend a little more time
with a certain coffee shop owner
who just happens to have the most beautiful eyes I've ever seen.
Adam, we don't really know each other.
Wasn't that the point of me staying?
What's the problem?
Hmm?
No one knows martial arts
without remembering where they learned it.
Chloe can't even hack a computer like you can.
And if you got it all from reading,
then where are the books?
Wow.
Clark must have really messed with your head.
Yeah, he did.
And I'm not gonna let that happen again.
Look, Lana, I like you.
And I've told you that.
Whatever your problems are,
I'm not gonna stick around to be one of them.
I'm not gonna.
I think you should go.
Bye.
Chloe.
Clark, don't sneak up on me like that.
Look, I talked to Lex, and they found your old computer at Luther Corp.
But the hard drive is gone.
Including all of my e-mail addresses.
Well, you think this is who took it.
She may be working for Lionel. Her name's Molly.
Riggs, yeah, I know.
And for once, the connection isn't Lionel.
I interviewed her for a story I did about a month ago.
About what?
Somerholt Neological Institute.
Somerholt?
Isn't that where Ryan used to be?
Yeah, the study is ESP.
That's why I started looking into the place.
Apparently, he isn't the only patient Dr. Garner held against their will.
Those methods are right out of the Mengele handbook.
Why was Molly there?
MIT recruited her at 15.
She was a total engineer whiz kid until she went homicidal on another student.
After her boyfriend...
...she had to break down the center to Somerholt.
Yeah, but Somerholt isn't exactly a psych ward.
For megalobraniacs, it is.
Why would she want to kill you?
Well, when I talked to her, she was pretty adamant that Dr. Garner had given her new life.
I had enough ammunition in that article to shut him down in a second.
Chloe, who else knows about this article?
Max.
Chloe, I've been looking into your Somerholt story.
I think you've got something here.
I'm sure you've got something.
Wait, slow down.
Threats are part of the job.
But I appreciate the heads up.
You'll get used to it.
You need something, Laureen?
Max?
Help!
Max!
Thanks for letting Chloe stay here, Lex.
Whatever I can do to help.
Yeah, this is the last place anybody would look for me.
would look for me.
Chloe, I'm sorry about what happened to your friend
at the Daily Planet.
You must have really had Garner over a barrel.
Yeah, well, I obviously didn't know what
I was getting myself into.
Just seems to be a nasty habit that I've picked up lately.
So your theory is that Garner has turned Molly
into his own email assassin using hypnotic suggestion?
It's not that far of a stretch.
Summerholt goes from studying the brain to controlling it.
It's a pretty amazing breakthrough
if you don't consider the application.
Well, there's no question.
When it comes to brain warping, Dr. Garner
is definitely the guy.
I'm going to go talk to Garner.
No, no, no, Clark. Don't, please.
It's too dangerous.
I'm not the one he's looking for.
It'll be all right.
Just don't leave the mansion.
I'll call you if I find anything.
I'll call you.
Chloe, I have my tech guys trying to track her.
I'm going to go see what they've got.
You can make yourself at home.
Awesome.
All right.
Clark Kent.
Here to abduct another one of my patients?
I think you'll find security has significantly increased
since your last visit.
I know what you and Molly are doing.
Molly?
Griggs?
She left us months ago.
She's sending out hypnotic emails.
It's not the kind of technology you pick up at Radio Shack.
Nor Summerholt, if that's what you're implying.
Mm.
Molly's already killed one reporter who's about to expose
everything you're doing here.
And she's going after another.
It's quite a coincidence.
Mr. Kent, this is a serious research institute.
I'm not going to involve Summerholt
in some imaginary high school investigation.
I don't think the police are going to see it that way.
Dr. Garner?
Cornell, could you show our friend to the door?
Lawrence, you have the key, right there.
This isn't what we're looking for.
Probably an agnostic's idea.
I mean, how would you know that?
That's wait until arms is back on your legs.
You think this is your last chance to kill me?
Time and time again, Lewis, I have a question for you.
Do you have evidence that you're responsible for any these
scams?
Yeah.
Department 927, please.
Hello?
Molly, something else has come up.
Library.
That's where you'll find all the books I was reading.
I thought you'd be on your way to Metropolis by now.
I was. I didn't want to leave things the way we did.
It can be a little abrupt.
That's one way of putting it.
You were driving me nuts.
I can see how strong you are, and then for some stupid reason
you retreated into this hurt little girl facade. It's ridiculous.
This is your way of ending things on better terms?
People here don't say what they think.
I wasn't trying to hide anything from you.
Then why are you so guarded?
You have to understand.
There are patterns.
There are patches of my life that I just can't piece back together.
And everyone that can answer those questions is gone.
It's kind of scary.
Smallville just seemed a little less terrifying than going to Metropolis on my own.
Crazy ninja girls and all.
I guess I just was moving a little too fast, so I'm sorry.
If I read something in our friendship that wasn't there.
I think it was a little too early to tell what was there.
Yeah.
I'm gonna miss my bus.
Lana, I...
I really hope you find a way to trust people again.
Because you're a really amazing person, and...
It would be a shame not to let someone get close enough to see that.
Adam, wait.
Were you serious about staying?
I'm sorry.
I'm starting to get a complex.
It seems all the women I find even remotely appealing turn out to be psychopaths.
Bards of a feather.
What did Garner do to you?
Lex, what are you doing here?
My tech guy traced her.
And you would be?
Is this what you're using to hurt my friends?
You know what? Get away from that!
Molly, you don't have to protect Garner. We know he's controlling you.
Look, there's only one person with that ability, and you're looking at her now.
Get away from the computer!
You looking for this, Clark?
How'd you get that?
Birds of a feather.
It wasn't Garner.
You're the one who developed the program, huh?
I pulled it from your disk drive.
You don't understand.
You don't know what it's like to be so different.
To see things other kids can't see.
To feel and to think about things they can't even imagine.
Molly, Garner's not helping you.
He made me feel normal, and I never thought that could happen.
If someone gave you that chance,
wouldn't you protect them too?
Clark, she sent an email right before we got here.
You recognize the address?
Mom.
Mrs. Kent?
Mrs. Kent, I got your call.
What did Clark find out?
I sent it to her.
What do you know?
They were already fixing up everything.
Those raw materials, including Miss Newsom's mechanism.
However, she should be safe.
She should be
going to that place before anybody can heat her.
Hey, Doreen.
Just let me know.
They're waiting for you.
We'll do our part.
Hurry up and comb those mills.
Sure.
Oh
No!
Mom!
What happened?
You okay?
I'm okay.
Okay, just keep an open mind.
So?
What do you think?
I think Norman Bates
would be right at home here.
Not exactly the tenant I had in mind.
Is that an offer?
We clear out all this junk and paint.
It could be a really cool space.
I negotiated a good deal on the rent
with the owner.
Well, I guess an upside would be
I wouldn't need an alarm clock.
I just wanted to...
The smell of fresh coffee would wake me up in the morning.
Well, unless you're making it.
If you stick around long enough,
I might just put you to work.
I appreciate you doing this for me,
but I don't want you to do it
because you feel sorry for me.
No.
That's not what this is about.
Trust me.
I'm just trying to help out a friend.
New computers?
Same old computers.
New Luther.
Lex returned them to me. No strings attached.
I guess he felt guilty about firing my dad.
At least you're up and running.
I'm running.
Sans cyber-stalker.
Your soul is still intact.
Yeah.
You know, with all this stuff with Molly,
it's just, there's a part of me
that feels like maybe I deserve it.
No, Chloe.
No, like it was my penance, you know,
for what I did to you.
You can't take all the blame.
You went to Lionel because I pushed you away.
That seems to be one of my hidden talents lately.
It's not so hidden.
You know, I never set out
to investigate you, Clark.
It just...
It was so flattering
that someone like that would be interested
in my work.
It made you feel like you mattered.
Yeah.
And then Lionel, like, set my dream out
right in front of me, and I just...
I don't know.
I gave in to all my worst instincts.
No, Chloe. He caught you at a weak moment.
We all have them.
When you found me at mine in Metropolis,
you didn't turn your back on me.
You gave me a second chance,
and I at least owe you the same.
I like that.
So what do we do now?
I mean, we can't just forget about everything that's happened.
Well,
you have to understand that there are some things
about me that'll never add up.
I know that.
Are you willing
to stop digging?
Yeah.
I mean, I figure you'll just
tell me when you think it's right.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
Mr. Luther,
you shouldn't know
when young Clark stopped by
that you wouldn't be far behind.
Any more attempts
on Chloe Sullivan's life would be...
ill-advised.
Molly seems to have
vanished into thin air.
I don't suppose
you'd know anything about that.
Molly's in the care of people who should be able to help her,
not exploit her.
Lex,
you're a smart man.
You know that the line has to be bent now and then
in order to make progress.
I believe there's
a difference between bent and broken.
You've never been so close to making a discovery
that you'd be willing to do almost anything
to see it through.
My work
could change the way that the world views intelligence.
Thon.
I don't think your research is worth the cost of innocent lives.
And I don't think
I have time for a morality lesson.
Excuse me.
Chloe's article's a real page-turner.
Almost worth killing over.
Wouldn't you say, Doctor?
What do you want, Lex?
Your health.
A few months ago,
I had an unfortunate session
of shock therapy that
basically erased seven weeks
of my life.
I want those seven weeks back.
Every two weeks.
To clean out my head.
And, I have three years left
of any AWS conflicts,
that I'll be at peace.
Find a護 ê эк.
Th Lageā жизни
Madastas
Pămâť
E incurna
desêm tipo midnight
Thank you.